

# PJOTR WISSE

#### SOFTWARE DEVELOPER / WEB DEVELOPER

### **BASIC INFO**

• Age: 17

• Nationality: Nederlands

• Gender: Man

More info: 84669.ict-lab.nl/

#### **PROFILE**

I am a student at the Grafisch Lyceum Rotterdam (GLR) and I am doing the Media technology course. Here I make websites, Interactive games and tools, and other software. I have worked with: HTML, CSS, Javascript, PHP, C #, SQL, and media management courses (Virtual machines, Databases, and Servers). Besides those features, I am very active, social, and quite funny.

### **SKILLS**

- I have a lot of knowledge in various subjects.
- Skills in programming and beta subjects (mathematics).
- Have a lot of Front-end Skills and Back-end skills.
- I can follow instructions and submit assignments on time.
- I am great at explaining IT topics to less experienced colleagues.
- I speak fluent English, I have a Cambridge C1 certificate. And I speak adequate German.

### **CHARACTERISTICS**

## WORKING EXPERIENCE

- Vast knowledge of computer science.
- An active worker.
- Social
- Good at video games
- A love of programming.

### CONTACT

Address: Fritsdiepenlaan 48, Den Haag Postal code: 2497 DK Contact-tel: +31 6 42899748 Email: PjotrW15@Gmail.com

### NATIONAAL VIDEOGAME MUSEUM (INTERNSHIP)

- I made sure to move arcades cabinets.
- Was an assistant at assembling hardware.
  I have monitored the arcades as security quard an
- I have monitored the arcades as security guard and a arcade tester.
- Especially had to troubleshoot Arcade's.

## NATIONAAL VIDEOGAME MUSEUM (ARCADE ENGINEER) JUN 2018 - JUL 2019

- Arcades assembled and tested.
- View the condition of old cabinets.
- Monitering the playhall.

OKT 2018 - OKT 2018

### **EDUCATION**

St.Paul College, The Hague, VMBO TL/MAVO (GLR)Grafisch Lyceum Rotterdam, MBO, Mediatechnology Application and Media Development

### DREAMS SURFSHOP (INTERNSHIP)

MAART 2018 - MAART 2018 (2 WEKEN)

- I've worked a lot with Photoshop here and I've learned how to run a business.
- Learned many economic skills.